DAY 9
FINAL SELECTION D-1
Only one day left
until the final selection.
Oh, gosh.
YOU WILL GET A "LET-IT-ALL-OUT DATE" TODAY
REQUEST ONE IF YOU WANT A FINAL SAY
It's Let-it-all-out Date.
Yeah.
A Let-it-all-out Date…
Let-it-all-out Date.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's their last chance to talk properly
to confess their feelings or apologize.
So I hope they just get
everything off their chest.
It's really the last chance.
I won't go if I don't pick anyone
and no one picks me, right?
- Right.
- Then, you don't get a date.
But someone can pick you.
Yeah, then you'll go on a date.
If Su-ji had made her decision,
whether it be a good one
or a bad one for me,
I thought she would pick me
to tell me her decision
on the Let-it-all-out Date.
Jung-yun has no other options.
We have five minutes left.
I requested the guaranteed
one-on-one secret date,
so it kept feeling one-sided.
I thought if Jeong-eun picked me
even if I didn't pick her,
then I could really…
I could confirm
that my feelings are reciprocated.
So I really hesitated
over whether to pick her or not.
Yesterday, I didn't pick anyone.
So I felt like I should
pick someone today no matter what.
I didn't hesitate much
after I got the text.
Su-ji will probably pick Hyuk-joon.
It was an easy choice to make.
If someone picks you,
you have to go on a date?
Yes, you have to.
- So one person can go on several dates.
- Yeah.
She must be anxious.
Hello. Soo-hyun, do you have a minute?
- Me?
- Can we talk for a bit?
What's going on?
Here. It's a letter.
- Gosh.
- Read that later.
And I won't be requesting a date today.
- You won't pick anyone? Why?
- No.
Today, I…
I don't feel like I have anything to say.
I wrote it all in the letter.
- Really?
- Yeah, I wrote it all down.
- So you won't go on a date?
- No.
Okay.
See you later, then.
She must feel confused.
As Tae-hoon gave me the letter,
he said he wouldn't request a date.
And in his letter,
he wrote that I was a charming person,
but he was worried
that because of his lukewarm reactions,
I might have been a bit hurt.
He said his feelings changed a bit, so I
wondered if that's what he was on about.
And if I requested a date with him,
I felt like I would be
pressuring him too much,
so I felt even more conflicted.
Tae-hoon didn't request a date,
but he let it all out in a letter.
Since Tae-hoon expressed his side,
Soo-hyun should just
accept it to avoid more hurt.
But I don't think Soo-hyun
can take it in right now
- Right.
- because she still likes him.
The letter is one thing,
but his decision not to request a date
- pretty much says it all.
- Obviously.
FINAL SELECTION D-1
THE LET-IT-ALL-OUT DATES BEGIN
Jin-woo.
I didn't request
a Let-it-all-out Date today.
But I was told I would go on a date,
so I hoped it was her.
Did Jeong-eun perhaps pick me?
Was it Jeong-eun?
- Oh my.
- It was Han-ju!
Han-ju worked up the courage in the end.
- You're here.
- I am.
It was Han-ju, who I talked to last night.
I wasn't disappointed.
I had been
kind of expecting it.
So, rather than disappointed,
I think I was in the process of giving up.
LET-IT-ALL-OUT-DATE
HAN-JU, JIN-WOO
I'm supposed to let it all out,
- but we talked a lot yesterday, so…
- We did.
I picked Jin-woo without hesitation.
I'm still interested in him,
and I was holding back
my feelings for Jin-woo until now
because I thought he had
no romantic interest in me at all.
So I didn't bother.
But since he told me
that I had been on his mind,
I decided to just express
my feelings from now on.
- Their talk last night gave her courage.
- Yes.
When I got back to my room last night,
I thought, "I should have
explained myself better."
"I was just talking nonsense."
I felt the same way.
I just talked without thinking.
- I was just rambling on.
- Same.
I went back and thought,
"I should've said this."
- Think it through and tell me now.
- Think it through now?
Want to go first?
We also talked about a lot of things
while playing games last night.
- Yeah.
- We indirectly expressed our feelings.
And I couldn't help but notice
the faces you made during that game.
Did I not hide my feelings well?
I was trying to.
Your mouth was smiling,
but your eyes weren't.
I thought I was so good
at keeping a poker face,
but everyone knew.
I've never seen someone look so forlorn.
Your smile didn't reach your eyes.
- I think she's always been on his radar.
- Yeah.
That's why he remembers
what kind of face she made.
Take your time.
I couldn't tell if you were considering me
for your final selection
or if you were just apologizing.
It wasn't very clear.
- Yeah, it was confusing.
- He wasn't clear.
Well, I'm still processing it myself.
I wonder if I'd become a bad guy
- if I changed my mind now.
- I see.
Before we talked yesterday,
I wasn't going to make a final selection.
- Right.
- The reason was…
I mean, you and I
have similar personalities,
and I know that
if I'm not interested in someone,
that never changes.
So, it felt pointless
to make an effort for a guy
who wasn't into me.
That's why I just kept
requesting dates with Hyuk-joon.
And that's why I thought
about opting out of final selection.
But I got the sense
that you might still be
considering me as an option,
so that's got me thinking.
I know it's a bit weird for me
to still not know my own feelings,
but I can't help feeling a bit unsure.
Yeah.
I understand that.
- I think Jin-woo feels bad and thankful.
- Yeah.
He feels bad about turning around
and saying he likes her at this point.
I didn't know you cried.
Can I ask why you cried?
It was because of my personal issues.
It wasn't because of a specific person.
But it did have a little to do with you.
Because I was scared of opening up
to someone who said they liked me.
Even though I really appreciated it.
I'm not really used to being
on the receiving end
of someone liking me.
So that was confusing.
I didn't know how
to navigate that going forward.
Talk about TMI.
I just didn't realize
you were such a deep-thinker.
If only we had a little bit more time.
- Yeah.
- That would've helped.
What is it?
Maybe I should have picked you
instead of Hyuk-joon for one of the dates.
Hyuk-joon just seemed
like more of an open door.
Well, maybe not that open.
But he seemed willing
to get to know other people more.
He was open to talking to other women.
I don't know. You just seemed too…
You just shunned everyone else.
- I swear I didn't.
- That's how it seemed.
What do you mean, I shunned you?
- Well, you did.
- When?
When did I ever?
I swear you did.
What does the final selection mean to you?
I think the final selection is basically…
I think I'll pick someone
I want to get to know
more seriously outside the show.
It feels like saying, "Do you want
to keep talking after the show?"
What does it mean to you?
I'm not sure.
I don't know
how much weight I should put on it.
- I guess it depends on how you see it.
- Yeah.
You just need to follow your heart.
At least, we get to talk like this
now that it's close to the end.
I'm not sure how seriously
we should take the final selection,
but…
But I'm just going to pick you.
So just know that.
Unbelievable.
She said she'll pick him.
Han-ju is so cool.
- Lee Han-ju!
- Gosh.
That right there was a declaration.
You don't need
to feel pressured or sorry at all.
She's so cool.
I can't look you in the eyes.
You're staring into the coffee.
How much time has passed?
Shall we check?
Han-ju, if you want to date Jin-woo,
cut back on the alcohol.
Can't Jin-woo just get better
at handling his drink?
I saw those pictures.
You're in a lot of the pictures.
STUNNING ROOMIES
Aren't there any photos of you?
No, I'm only in the group shots.
I don't really like my face.
Why not? You're the best-looking guy here.
It's so great
how she keeps telling him that.
- Seriously.
- It is.
If you keep blurting that out,
you might get a lot of backlash.
She finds him cute. That's what matters.
- Right?
- Of course.
Yeah, all that matters is what she thinks.
Even before I came here,
everyone was asking
if I got acupuncture in my head.
- A Korean medicine doctor joke.
- You should have kept quiet.
Then you could've escaped the abuse.
Has anyone told you
that you look like a celebrity?
Me? Is there someone who comes to mind?
Someone just crossed my mind,
but I don't know if I should say it.
Keep it in mind and tell me later
when we get back.
Just write it down somewhere
so that no one finds out.
- Go on. Say it.
- Tell her.
You look a bit like Moon Chae-won.
Oh… Damn it.
I told you to write it down secretly.
I can't go down alone.
Yes!
- It's fine.
- She's blushing.
I think she's even more into him now.
Let's get going.
The weather's nice.
I used to care about a guy's height.
Sorry I'm a short king.
It's fine. If you were also tall,
I would have thrown myself at you.
I'm the only guy who's 170-something.
I think I got my feelings across.
I told him that I would choose him
for the final selection,
so a weight has been lifted off my chest.
WHAT DO YOU LIKE SO MUCH ABOUT JIN-WOO?
His face is closest to my ideal type.
And at first, I thought he was
just my type looks-wise.
But his personality is also my type.
He seems
like someone who is
quite mature and thoughtful,
and I find that really attractive.
But I'm curious how Jin-woo feels.
- We're curious, Jin-woo.
- I want to know too.
Honestly, I felt a little swayed.
Just when I started to wish
I had deeper talks with Han-ju,
she expressed her interest once again,
so my heart fluttered.
But for me to turn around now
and suddenly decide to be
romantically interested in Han-ju…
It feels like
a disrespectful thing to do to her.
So I still feel a bit torn.
- If only they had a bit more time.
- Yeah.
They should talk more after the show.
They should.
What I think is really cool
is that Han-ju and Jin-woo's dynamic
resulted in Han-ju getting a bit hurt,
but she still gave it another go
by requesting the Let-it-all-out Date
and ended by saying
she'd pick him for the final selection.
- Yes.
- She went that far
despite getting hurt.
- Exactly.
- That was really cool.
Her vibe was different
from her dates with Hyuk-joon.
- Totally different.
- That's right.
And Jin-woo has started to feel a spark.
- Yes.
- Exactly.
He sensed how Jeong-eun felt
and was slowly giving up
- when Han-ju confessed to him.
- Perfect timing.
Of course, he's swayed.
- True. He's human, after all.
- Yes.
It's Soo-hyun.
White pants.
Tense shoulders.
It's Seung-hyun.
- It's the SH couple!
- Hello.
Hello.
- You're wearing blue today.
- Yeah. Hi.
Gosh.
LET-IT-ALL-OUT-DATE
SOO-HYUN REQUESTED THE DATE
Soo-hyun requested it!
Seung-hyun must be so happy.
- Hello.
I was just… I was a bit shocked
because I didn't expect
to go on any dates.
So I was happy.
- Hello.
Gosh.
Goodness.
She's shy. The one who requests it
is always the shy one.
The more they learn about
their feelings, the shyer they get.
Thank you.
It looks so tasty.
Listen to that sizzling.
- I love it.
- Same.
Which pork cut do you prefer?
- I like them both.
- Yeah?
- You don't have a preference? Really?
- No.
Did you request a date today?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Well…
- I told you how I felt yesterday.
- Yeah.
But honestly,
I was so nervous before I went in.
I also had butterflies.
Anyway, my interest in you right now is…
- You're my top pick right now.
- Oh, your top pick.
I'll give it some thought.
- I'll have a think.
- Okay.
And I figured
that you needed time
to think things through,
so I didn't request a date.
- I see.
- He wanted to give her time.
He didn't want to pressure her.
He's so…
He's so "unrude."
He's the opposite of rude.
- Oh, he's the opposite?
- Yeah.
- He's "unrude."
- Unlike Tae-hoon, who is rude.
- He's respectful.
- He is.
- He lacks rudeness.
- He's "unrude."
He's a ball of good manners.
He's super courteous.
- Yes.
- He's "unrude."
- Do you think it's cooked?
- Yes.
- Here you go.
- Let's eat.
Thank you.
Oh my.
- He gave her the first piece.
- That's not an easy thing to do.
It looks so tasty.
Go ahead and eat first.
No, let's eat together.
Together? Right, we should do that.
Have you organized your thoughts?
Even until this morning--
- You're not sure?
- Yeah, I was in my room
wondering what to do.
I get that.
- It's hard.
- It is.
- What about you?
- Huh?
- How do you feel?
- About what?
Do you feel like your mind
is made up today?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Really?
I think I've pretty much decided.
- Yeah.
I was so thankful
for the things you said yesterday.
- Really?
- Yeah.
That's a relief. I was a bit worried
that maybe I pressured you.
But after I told you, to be honest,
I feel kind of bad for saying this,
but I felt much better.
- So…
- Yeah?
- So, for me…
I felt good about having had
that talk with you.
What I felt when we talked yesterday
was that you must have
put so much thought into it.
- I could feel that.
- Really?
- I'm glad that came across.
- Yeah.
- I thought I was done deciding.
- Really?
Yeah.
I felt like I had pretty much
made my mind up.
I thought things were decided.
But my mind changed
after the secret dates yesterday.
Really?
So I have a lot on my mind now.
But I didn't feel pressured at all.
That's good because…
You said your mind was made up,
but I might have…
I might have shaken things up.
One of them should say
something a bit flirty at this point.
You might be right.
- You just saw that, right?
- No, I didn't.
You might be right.
So, has something changed for you?
A change?
I would be lying
if I said nothing's changed.
Okay.
- But my mind's just all over the place.
- You're still confused?
In that case,
after you think things through…
- We can talk again then.
- Yeah, that's right.
Okay. I'll have a think.
They're taking too long to think.
But Soo-hyun's reaction
is a bit lukewarm, right?
Yeah, it's not enough.
I want to see a bit more chemistry.
- A bit more spark.
- It's lukewarm.
- The vibe is a bit dry.
- You think so?
- She should have said, "You shook me up."
- Yeah, that's good.
- That would seal the deal.
- Or how about this?
"I liked that you raised the stakes."
- No?
- That would've been better?
That doesn't quite work.
- You don't think so?
- Is this a poker game?
Hey, Eun-ji. Do you think
they're playing poker?
"I liked that you raised the stakes
and pulled out a flush."
So funny.
I just wish it was a bit more exciting.
- They need more heat.
- Raise the heat.
- Just a bit.
- I feel like they're close.
Just a bit more flirting.
- Shake things up a bit.
- They can't hear us, can they?
No, they can't.
The weather's so nice.
Let's go.
- It is so nice to be by the ocean.
- Yeah.
The view over there is really pretty.
- You're right!
- Yeah.
- It's really pretty over there.
It's pretty anywhere you look.
It's so stunning here.
They look so good together.
The color's so lovely.
They look amazing together!
- This place is amazing. I owe it to you.
- Yeah.
Should I try taking a photo?
It looks great! I want to take one too.
- They should take one together.
- Yes, take a couple selfie!
Come on, Soo-hyun!
- I could stay here for a good two hours.
- Really?
How nice.
- You'd think they're married from behind.
- Yeah.
Shall we go?
- Shall we?
- I want to enjoy the view a bit more, but…
Leave now so we want to come back again.
- That's right! Clever.
- Wisdom comes with age, you know.
Not bad.
He's doing great.
I think being brave definitely paid off.
Personally, I prefer a partner
I feel comfortable around,
and the conversation flowed
really well with Soo-hyun,
and I felt a connection.
And she has a really pretty smile.
- Oh my gosh.
- Yes!
You should have told her that.
- "You have a great smile."
- He has a great smile too.
So I felt very attracted to her.
She is my top pick right now.
- He's really bounced back.
- This is great.
I was able to get to know him better.
And that was nice.
I did feel a bit of a spark with him,
and I do feel more interested now.
She used her last chance for a date
on Seung-hyun and not Tae-hoon.
- She did.
- Good choice.
For the final selection,
will she pick Tae-hoon, who she likes,
or Seung-hyun, who likes her?
What do you think?
I really hope she'll pick Seung-hyun.
But there's a chance that she…
- Because she liked Tae-hoon a lot.
- She did.
I'm worried she'll just go
for what she wants and pick Tae-hoon.
I also hope she'll pick Seung-hyun,
but I'm not too sure
because the smoothies
could give Tae-hoon a leg up.
That's true.
- Who is it?
- Who's this?
It's a great location.
- Oh, it's Su-ji.
- It's Su-ji.
If she requested this date,
I think it will be with Hyuk-joon.
Yeah, that's for sure.
Hello.
- We were right.
- A last-minute shake-up.
A showdown.
I feel so nervous.
LET-IT-ALL-OUT DATE
HYUK-JOON, SU-JI
Please.
Have you been waiting long?
- No, I just got here.
- Really?
I see.
LET-IT-ALL-OUT DATE
SU-JI REQUESTED THE DATE
The sun's so bright.
- It is.
- Yeah.
I think she'll really shake things up.
I wanted to talk with Hyuk-joon
since he kept catching my attention.
So I wanted to figure out my own feelings.
I also went on the date
to tell him that I'd been noticing him.
That's so Su-ji.
I didn't expect to see you.
- Really? You didn't expect it?
- No, I didn't.
I just wanted to talk to you.
I see.
When we went to the theme park,
I suddenly found it hard
to look you in the eyes.
- Why?
- So I thought about why that was.
At first, I tried hard to find a reason,
but I think I feel drawn to you.
So…
That's why I requested this date.
I had no idea.
- Really?
- Yeah, because you never asked
to talk to me after that
or you know…
Even when we hung out alone,
all we did was eat chocolate.
- You seemed to really like chocolate.
- Yeah.
Honestly, I did wonder if I should
request a date with you yesterday.
I ended up not doing it,
but I kind of regretted it.
Even though I decided
not to do it at that moment,
I went back and forth a lot,
so I would have regretted it less
if I had just gone through with it.
I just…
I decided to just go for it.
I don't want to keep hesitating.
She's being so direct.
Hyuk-joon's going to be confused again.
- You can see it in his eyes already.
- Exactly.
Oh, no.
Have you given anyone a gift?
Yeah, I did end up using a coupon.
But I used it a bit late,
so I don't think he's seen it.
Hyuk-joon got gloves as a gift.
Hold on.
- Could it be?
- Were they from Su-ji?
I want to ask you what you did yesterday.
- Yesterday--
- "Who did you meet?"
I want to ask where you went
and what you did.
- It's a secret.
- It is, isn't it?
I nearly told everyone too.
Hyuk-joon's growing conflicted.
Do you still feel the same way,
or have you made your mind up?
I've made up my mind now.
He's being straightforward.
- Really?
- I've talked now
with most of the women.
I was concerned about
whether having shared interests
was more important,
or whether being drawn to someone was.
It came down to which is more important.
I gave it a lot of thought.
And I'm leaning toward the person
I feel drawn to.
I'm so curious. Can't you give me a hint?
- About who that person is?
- Yeah.
It's Hyun-seo.
Wow, Hyuk-joon.
He's being so honest. Wow.
Yeah, Hyun-seo is my pick.
- I saw that coming.
- From the start,
we just kept getting
- randomly matched on dates.
- Yeah.
And the conversation flowed really well.
- She stayed on your mind.
- Yeah.
She did.
He must feel sure of his feelings now.
Yeah, he's stopped straying.
It won't get awkward between us now
that I requested this date, will it?
- Not at all.
- I hope you won't take it too seriously.
- I won't feel pressured or anything.
- That's good.
- Since we went to the Sparks House,
- Yeah.
we shared the same goal.
- We did.
- We wanted to talk to everyone.
And this date
is the last chance to talk one-on-one.
- Exactly.
- It's the last chance, so…
- We won't get another chance after this.
- That's right.
- That's how I see it.
- I didn't want to waste this chance.
I thought I would really regret it
if I let another chance just slide by
because I didn't use yesterday's chance.
No, you didn't.
I am a bit disappointed
since I wanted to get to know him more.
I think if we'd had more time,
we would've had a chance.
But I don't have any regrets.
Su-ji has an attractive personality.
And I enjoyed our conversation
at the Sparks House.
But she just feels like a little sister.
I see her more like a sister
than a romantic interest.
She's cute.
But I think I'm more attracted
to sophisticated women.
- He means Hyun-seo.
- Yes.
Hyun-seo's the one for him.
He did get to know everyone
through all those dates.
Oh, I guess it's time to go back.
THE LET-IT-ALL-OUT DATE IS OVER
PLEASE LEAVE THE PREMISES, SU-JI
Oh, Hyuk-joon stays?
I'll get going.
- Hang on.
- You must have a busy day.
That's not it.
Don't lie. You know you do. Why play dumb?
That's so unattractive.
I'm glad someone said it.
- Well done, Su-ji.
- Nice going.
- Oh, Su-ji.
- Look at her face.
Can you rewind?
Don't lie. You know you do. Why play dumb?
That's so unattractive.
- I'm off.
- Why so harsh?
Wow.
I'm so glad she said that.
I think a lot of people
will be glad she said that.
- Hyuk-joon definitely…
- Yes?
During his time on the show,
he behaved quite badly
in a lot of ways, didn't he?
- You're right.
- He was indecisive.
He was.
- But he's ending things on a clear note.
- He is.
He's being very direct.
He's on his best behavior now.
I think Hyun-seo was also very wise.
If she'd gone, "What the heck?
Why are you going on those dates?"
- They might have parted ways for good.
- That's right.
But she was like, "Go on, then.
Talk to other women."
She was quite laid back about it.
- Yes.
- I think that's why Hyuk-joon
said that he's attracted
to someone sophisticated.
I think he said that
because he feels grateful
about how she handled it.
- Yes.
- But Hyuk-joon really needs to know that.
He needs to know how understanding
and considerate Hyun-seo has been.
- Yes.
- She really likes him.
- Yeah, he needs to know.
- He does.
That's right.
Hyuk-joon's arduous search for love
is finally over.
"Arduous search for love."
- After all that wandering…
- It was a long journey.
I expect Hyun-seo will come next.
- Did they cross paths? What is it?
- Is it a run-in?
- Jeong-eun?
- What?
She's bumped into Su-ji.
- Fancy seeing you here.
- How crazy.
- You must be here for the view.
- Yeah.
- I wanted to check out whatever's here.
- It's gorgeous here, isn't it?
I wonder what could be here.
- There's something interesting in there.
- I thought it might be hidden.
- See you later.
- Okay, bye!
- They're both embarrassed.
- Yes.
- Oh my gosh.
- Jeong-eun picked Hyuk-joon too.
- They were at the Sparks House together.
- That's true.
- Hey.
- Oh, hi.
I just bumped into someone.
LET-IT-ALL-OUT-DATE
HYUK-JOON, JEONG-EUN
- You guys are roomies.
- That's right.
- It's nice to see you.
- You too.
- It's so nice and sunny here.
- Yeah.
It's so warm.
He was someone I was still curious about.
We had said that we should talk
one-on-one some time.
But we didn't have a chance.
So I requested the date to make it happen.
- Did you know I would come?
- No, I didn't.
- Right?
- Yeah, I had no idea.
I told you I would make a chance
to talk to you one-on-one,
but I was never able to.
But I like how I look today,
so I couldn't let this chance go to waste.
Hyuk-joon's growing awkward.
It would be a shame
not to take this chance, right?
I really appreciate you being
so honest with me
and for requesting this date.
But I really never imagined this.
I thought you had your mind made up.
You seemed to be
talking a lot with Jin-woo,
and I noticed him being
very attentive to you.
- Yeah.
- Right? So…
I thought the two of you
- had something going on.
- You thought we had something.
But did you want to talk a bit more?
- With who?
- Me.
Joon, we believe in you.
In Joon we trust!
- I used to.
- Right.
But when I heard that you gave
a gift to Jin-woo as well…
I think gift-giving carries
a big meaning to me.
Why are you so obsessed with gifts?
I find his gift-obsession so funny.
- Why is he so obsessed about it?
- Seriously.
He's admitting that gift-giving
means a bit more to him.
It just kills me
- how obsessed he is.
- Gift-giving means a lot to him.
It's a huge deal.
So I felt a bit thrown off
when I found out you gave us both a gift.
Rather than someone
who makes me feel confused,
I prefer someone who is
direct and straightforward.
And someone was very direct with me
and honestly expressed
her feelings for me.
So I feel more attracted to her
because of that.
In a way, I got rejected.
I kind of wanted to run from it,
like I did yesterday.
But I got over that fear
and faced up to it.
That itself was enough
to make me feel relieved.
Su-ji and Jeong-eun's honesty
is so admirable.
And it seems like Hyuk-joon
has really made up his mind now.
- It's such a relief.
- It really is time for them
- to get ready for the final selection.
- Right.
It's Hyuk-joon. He needs to get going.
He needs to go to her.
Hello.
You're here. Hello.
- We're outdoors.
- Yeah, we're having hoe.
- Finally.
- At last.
Yeah.
LET-IT-ALL-OUT DATE
HYUK-JOON, HYUN-SEO
They have yellowtail. Do you want some?
LET-IT-ALL-OUT DATE
THEY BOTH REQUESTED THE DATE
- They both wanted it.
- That's so nice.
- Here it comes!
- Is it here?
- Thank you.
Wow.
- We need a photo.
- Oh my gosh.
- We'll have to show off later.
- We should.
- Cheers.
- It's so good.
- So tasty.
We haven't seen Hyun-seo
laugh like that in a while.
What if we get too tipsy?
- We might get all drunk.
- Exactly.
They seem at ease now.
Yeah.
- Is it good?
- Yes.
How about one of you
feed the other person?
It tastes so good.
It's so nice and chewy.
This is nice.
They're finally on a proper date.
Oh, by the way,
did you go to the Post Office?
- When? Yesterday?
- Yeah.
- Were the gloves from Hyun-seo?
- Maybe.
LAST NIGHT
CHOI HYUK-JOON
She got me gloves.
- He's over the moon.
- His reaction is better
- than everyone else's.
- It makes it worth giving him a gift.
It does.
I got gloves.
It came with a letter.
The tone of the letter…
KEEP YOUR HANDS WARM
THE LAST TWO DAYS
…was just so Hyun-seo.
She talks in a distinct way.
- Like, kind of instructional.
- She talks like a commander.
I think she tried
to make it really obvious.
That was probably her way
of directly expressing her feelings to me.
I had hoped for Hyun-seo
to be a little bit more expressive
about her feelings,
and she couldn't have done it better.
I was honestly really touched.
He's so over the moon.
- We should learn from him.
- Yeah.
When I get a gift,
I'm like, "There's no need."
I should be like Hyuk-joon.
- Be more excited.
- We should.
"Oh my gosh!"
"I've really wanted this!"
I'm realizing that's how we should react.
We're learning a lot from him, seriously.
Thanks, Joon.
- Thank you, Joon.
- Thanks.
When I picked out the gloves,
I wasn't sure if they were a good gift.
I was very torn.
I really like wearing gloves.
- Really?
- Yeah, I do.
So I've put them on display.
I hung up the gloves like this.
Really? Where?
- I hung them on a clothes hanger.
- Really?
They're back to how it was at the start.
He's looking at her the same.
I even took a photo.
She must find that adorable.
He's acting less pretentious now.
- Yeah.
- He's back to his old self.
It was a great gift.
I thought, "She's good at this."
You said you weren't,
but you're good at picking gifts.
- But I really…
- Yeah?
I thought you were really cute yesterday.
What do you mean?
After we were all done hanging out
in the Post Office together,
when you and the guys
were heading back inside,
you were like, "Should I head back?"
Are you going back to your room?
I want to wash up.
Go on in.
Bye.
Should I head back?
I thought that was cute.
You were like a puppy.
If you think they're cute,
it means you love them.
If you find them cute, it's game over.
You were cute.
I didn't want to do anything
that could cause a misunderstanding.
Yeah, if you had kept confusing me,
- I wouldn't be here with you right now.
- Exactly.
He came to his senses.
I'm so proud of him.
If he confuses her again,
she'll have to rip his clothes to shreds.
- After the show is over,
- Yeah?
is there anything you want to do with me?
Art exhibitions.
You want to go to exhibitions?
That means he wants
to see her outside the show.
You mentioned that you like exhibitions.
I enjoy things like…
I don't talk during the exhibition,
but after the exhibition,
- I like going to a cafe and…
- Sharing your thoughts?
- Yeah.
- Isn't Hyun-seo a curator?
She is.
We'd better take a trip
to Apgujeong sometime soon
- together.
- Right.
- There are a lot of galleries there.
- Yeah.
I think it will be fun to go together.
Since we met on Jeju Island,
it's kind of hard
to picture life back in Seoul.
- I think it will feel weird.
- Yeah.
Meeting in Seoul will be…
It will definitely feel special.
- Right.
- It's like we are
stepping into a different world.
- Yeah.
- Right?
It's like we've been in the Digimon world
and now we're back in the real world.
- Yeah.
- They're like a couple already.
It felt like a taste
of how we'd be in the real world.
It was like the wall between fantasy
and reality came tumbling down.
That wall got knocked down.
It made me go, "Oh, right.
We'll see each other in Seoul too."
I'm looking forward to it,
and I feel excited.
I want to keep getting to know her
on a deeper level.
I think it will be a lot of fun.
I'm really curious
what the future has in store.
But for me, rather than messaging,
- I prefer talking on the phone.
- Really?
And I prefer meeting up
to talking on the phone.
- Calls make me a bit anxious.
- I know.
Really? How do you know that?
- You told me.
- I did not.
- What are you--
- You…
- You did tell me.
- No, I didn't.
I only told Seo-yoon today
that I don't like talking on the phone.
Really?
Who are you…
Who are you confusing me with?
- Shall we toast?
- Who are you mixing me up with?
Let's clink glasses.
I've never told you that.
But most people nowadays
don't like talking on the phone.
He handled that smoothly.
Jeez.
I messed up.
- Shall I jump into the water?
- Yeah.
Go on. Dive in.
It's okay. I understand.
You've been on dates with a lot of women,
so you must get confused
about who said what.
Do I need to kneel down and grovel?
Yes.
I'm going to throw you into the water.
There's a sting in what she said.
She'll never let this go.
Oh, tomorrow is the final selection.
- Today is the last day.
- Yeah.
Honestly, when we got the text
about the Let-it-all-out Date,
I thought, "I have nothing to let out."
"Who should I let it all out to?"
I just read the first line.
It said, "If there is someone
you want a date with…"
And there was someone
I wanted to go on a date with.
So you picked me?
Of course, I did!
Why ask the obvious?
- Well done.
- Wait, did you not pick me?
- I'm sorry.
- Really?
No. Actually, I am sorry.
Why?
- This is such a betrayal.
- No way.
Of course, I picked you.
I didn't even hesitate!
Same here! I texted straight away.
I've never hesitated.
I always picked you, Hyuk-joon.
There you go.
Hyun-seo went through a lot emotionally.
That's right.
Currently, my top pick is Hyuk-joon.
Watch how her face changes.
My top pick is Hyuk-joon.
- She was upbeat until this point.
- My top pick is Hyuk-joon.
And I don't have a second pick anymore.
My top pick is still Hyuk-joon.
Oh my gosh.
Her clothes got darker too.
This was the toughest day.
I still pick Hyuk-joon.
Hyuk-joon is my top pick right now.
DO YOU HAVE A SECOND PICK?
I don't have one.
I would like a date with Hyuk-joon.
- She's been so consistent.
- She has.
It's always been Hyuk-joon.
Gosh. Look at the sunset.
Wow, it's beautiful.
They look like a real couple too.
- They look good.
- Look how they're standing.
I'll take a photo of you.
It's like a scene from a K-drama.
Do you trust me?
Make me look like a model, okay?
- Goodness.
- Yes! They're taking one together.
One, two, three.
It's their first couple photo.
Yes.
We got to capture the moment.
Talk about romantic.
Wow, what a stunning background.
- Wow, this is…
- It's like a painting.
Should we head down?
- Let's go.
- Watch your step.
Thank you.
Look at that.
Jeez, look at that.
They held hands!
They didn't grab the wrist or anything.
- Gosh.
- Can you make it down?
Be careful.
- Why let go?
- Grab it again.
Hold hands again while you walk.
I feel like I'm blushing even now.
The stairs were a bit steep,
so when we walked down,
I helped her out a bit.
I felt butterflies.
But then, I immediately looked away.
Because he felt awkward?
I felt too shy to look at her for a while.
His hand was very soft.
It felt a bit…
It felt electric.
Of all the dates I've been on,
it was the most memorable moment.
What a meaningful date.
This date for Hyun-seo and Hyuk-joon was…
- It's washed away all my anger.
- Yes.
Isn't it the first time anyone's
held hands since the partner dancing?
- That's right.
- It's the first time.
Oh my gosh.
- Gifts mean more to Hyuk-joon than most.
- That's right.
And he confirmed the gloves
were from Hyun-seo.
- It's perfect.
- Yes.
They're a done deal, right?
- Of course.
- Absolutely.
Lovely weather.
Ring his doorbell. I'll wait with you.
Is she planning on talking to Tae-hoon?
No wonder she wants to clear things up.
Even if they don't get an outside date,
- they should talk.
- They need closure.
- Yeah.
- They do.
Someone's coming.
- Let's talk.
- What's up?
- Okay.
- I see you were asleep.
- You just woke up, right?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Did you have a nice date?
Yeah, we talked.
Well done.
- Go on.
- You start.
You go first.
I had a date with Seung-hyun.
We had black pork
and took a stroll on the beach.
- Sounds like a nice date.
- Yeah, it was fun.
Have you organized your thoughts?
Yeah. I gave you my answer today.
Honestly, there is someone
who likes you more than I do.
- What?
- Huh?
So you've given up?
It's not that I've given up.
It's just right that you choose him.
That's how I see it.
What is he saying?
Seung-hyun asked me if I minded,
and I told him I didn't mind
because I think he likes you more.
So I told him I'm fine
with whatever happens.
It's right for me to go to him?
I can't offer you as much as he can.
- He's handling it like a coward.
- He is.
It could be better for him just to say,
"I don't like you that much."
Does that clear things up for you?
- She doesn't look satisfied.
- It doesn't sit right with her.
Let's go.
Shall we? That's everything?
- You don't have anything more to say?
- No.
You don't have any more questions?
- Will you make a final selection?
- Final selection?
- Yes.
I can't tell you.
I feel like you're winding me up.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
I don't know
if I'm just slow on the uptake,
but I was a bit confused.
In a way, it feels like a rejection,
but it also feels like
he was being considerate of me.
And in a way, it also seems
like he's being considerate of Seung-hyun.
So I was confused
about how I should take it.
It didn't feel like he was
being considerate of anyone.
"You are very attractive,
but someone who appreciates
your charm more than I do
is Seung-hyun,
so I think I should step aside."
- It's so ambiguous.
- That's just
- him not being honest.
- It's an excuse, right?
Tae-hoon just doesn't
like Soo-hyun that much.
That's right.
In a way, from Tae-hoon's perspective,
he was rejecting her in his own way.
But I'm not sure Soo-hyun
will be able to accept it.
She really liked him.
- She liked him more.
- Yeah, so it will be harder on her.
She seems very confused.
Oh, dear. What will she do?
Did you have a date? Who was it with?
- It was with Hyuk-joon.
- Me too.
- Did you not meet Jung-yun today?
- No, I didn't.
- Jung-yun didn't pick you?
- He didn't request a date?
No, he didn't.
- But I should go talk to him now.
- Oh, me too.
- What for?
- Is she going to end things?
She'll tell him once and for all.
Yeah, so I…
- Hey, Jung-yun. Let's talk.
- Hello.
- Jin-woo, can you step out for a bit?
- Can we talk?
- Okay.
- Sure.
Did you have ramyeon earlier?
- Did you eat?
- Yeah, I did.
Well done.
Did you go to the Post Office
this morning?
- Did you check your cabinet?
- Yeah, I did.
I got you a bracelet.
Yeah, thanks.
THIS MORNING
Yesterday, you asked me
if I'd tell you once I've made up my mind.
Yeah.
- And I told you I would.
- Right.
Well…
I feel so comfortable around you,
- and you're the closest to my ideal type.
- Right.
But to be honest,
I realized yesterday that my feelings
probably won't turn romantic.
I feel really thankful,
and I'm sorry that I can't
reciprocate your feelings.
But that is…
Feelings can't always be mutual.
To be honest, even so…
I was waiting for you
to come and talk to me like this.
I feel like I took too long.
- Yeah, but the time we have is…
- It's very short.
I thought it would be nice
to have a bit more time.
That's why I feel…
At the end of the day, we did
what we could in the time we were given.
So, I think it's okay.
Jung-yun's the one doing the comforting.
You're a really understanding person.
But you know…
I came onto this show thinking
it would be good to gain
something from this experience.
- Did you?
- So compared to how I was before--
- You've grown?
- Yeah, if I've changed at all,
I think that's a pretty great takeaway.
Do you feel like
you've changed for the better?
Yeah, I do.
I do feel like I've grown a little.
I'm a little bit different
from how I was before.
There were things I wanted to try,
and I went for it.
I don't want you to feel too awkward
- or uneasy.
- I don't feel uneasy.
I want you to take it easy.
I want you to do whatever suits you too.
Jung-yun's really matured.
He's so cool.
I feel like he really grew from the pain.
I came here to go with the flow
and follow my heart.
- That's why I came on the show.
- That's so admirable.
- We don't have long left.
- Exactly.
We should enjoy
the little time we have left.
Let's enjoy it.
- Shall we go?
- Okay.
- Thanks for your time.
- Sure.
I'm sorry if I took so long.
No, it's really okay.
Honestly,
I kind of expected it.
The longer she took to think about it…
the more I saw this coming.
I would be lying if I said
I wasn't disappointed.
I am obviously disappointed.
But even so,
since being on the show,
the things I've thought and felt,
and the things I did
to turn those things into action…
He expressed himself as much as he could.
- He did.
- Yeah.
I feel
very proud of myself and satisfied.
So even though I am disappointed,
I'm still pleased.
That's how I'd wrap this up.
He experienced a lot,
especially emotionally,
and that's a big deal.
- He's gained a lot from it.
- He's learned a lot.
And he really put in a lot of effort.
He went all out,
starting with his makeover.
- He went on so many mock blind dates.
- That's right.
His eyes are
- very soulful.
- He's so handsome.
He's got a cool aura.
- Yeah.
- He does.
He's one of us.
Let's just move on.
During my time on this show,
it's true that you are the guy
I've felt the most drawn to.
And in terms of you as a person,
I thought you were a good catch.
So even though I did feel
like you were moving a bit fast,
I wanted to see it through to the end.
But honestly, there's just one thing
about you that concerned me.
- The fact that you're a student.
- I see.
When I imagine going back
to the real world,
I can already see
that it'll be hard to make things work.
It makes a bigger difference
than you might think.
So my mind was made up today.
But I regret not being more relaxed
and having more fun with you
these last few days.
I was just conflicted the whole time,
only to reach this decision.
So I feel really bad about that.
No, it's okay.
I saw this coming,
but to actually hear it…
- It's hard, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Thanks for telling me, though.
I'm sorry you had to choose
such a complicated girl.
No, it's fine.
Okay.
I'll get up first.
Okay. I'll stay a bit longer.
Take time to collect yourself.
Jeong-eun told me that I did my best
and that really helped,
but she wasn't ready
to reciprocate my feelings.
I know that she was telling me
not to blame myself,
but I can't help feeling self-conscious
about being a student,
and I wonder if things would've been
different if I was more good-looking.
It's hard not to be hard on myself.
Jin-woo has a tendency
- to find fault with himself.
- That's right.
- So that's a bit worrying.
- It is.
But once he enters the working world,
he can naturally shake off
that kind of insecurity.
But I think Jeong-eun
just wasn't that into him.
- Yeah.
- That's true too.
- That's a big part.
- Yeah.
She has clear standards,
but she also wasn't into him enough
to let go of those standards.
- It wasn't enough.
- Exactly.
You're right.
- She wasn't that into him.
- Exactly.
Her feelings weren't that strong.
I feel so much better.
Yeah.
Have you decided to just go for it?
Are you all in?
- What do you mean?
- What?
Didn't the talk go well?
- Did it not go well?
- Of course. It went fine.
She rejected me, basically.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Why?
- Spill the beans.
What do you mean why?
I just thanked her
for being honest with me.
I just got flat-out rejected too.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It wasn't a total surprise,
but I feel a bit glum
now that she's confirmed it.
I kind of got my hopes up.
But I had a bad feeling
as soon as we sat down to talk.
I got the sense
it would be a rejection.
And I didn't think
it would matter that I'm a student,
but she told me that was the reason, so…
That makes it harder.
It makes me think that even if
I think something's not a big deal,
it might not be the case for someone else.
Whether it's my height or my job.
I thought being a good person
was all that mattered, but…
I think she just saw me
as a good person, and that's it.
- But it's different for everyone.
- Of course.
- He shouldn't be hard on himself.
- No.
Anyway, so I was rejected
once and for all.
Don't cry today.
Should we all have a drink here today?
Should I get wasted again?
I shouldn't have put in so much effort.
Want me to get you a drink?
It might be hard right now, but…
I know.
We've spent an entire ten days here.
Yeah.
Of course, it hurts.
Time will heal all wounds.
I took down the good luck fish.
Didn't you notice it's gone?
Did you? Why did you take it down?
It kept reminding me of her.
Then it's good you took it down.
Good luck fish, my ass.
No, I appreciate the gesture.
It was a gift, after all.
She was being thoughtful.
Yeah.
This heartbreak is making me sleepy.
He's having a hard time
because his feelings were genuine.
- It's because he went all in.
- Yes.
Gosh, it's the final day.
The day of the final selection is here.
Oh my gosh.
The final selection process is simple.
Once you make your selection,
you will wait at the designated spot.
If the person you picked shows up,
you will be a final couple.
Eternal singles
who don't have a final pick
- can choose to opt out.
- That's right.
I wonder how many final couples we'll get.
- Who is it?
- It looks like Hyuk-joon.
I will pick Hyun-seo
for the final selection.
And to me, the final selection means…
"Shall we get to know each other
on a deeper level?"
That's what it means to me.
So there's no reason for me
not to choose her.
He said he has no reason
not to choose her!
HYUK-JOON'S FINAL SELECTION: HYUN-SEO
Choosing someone means
taking the relationship a step further.
And I was a bit anxious
about messing things up.
So I did go back and forth
on whether to make a final selection.
Looks like she really felt
the weight of this selection.
HYUK-JOON, HYUN-SEO
FINAL SELECTION
They did it!
Success.
We got the first couple of Season Two.
- Hyuk-joon and Hyun-seo.
- Wow.
- You got here first.
- Yeah.
What do you think?
I prepared all this silver grass for you.
You really went all out.
Honestly, Hyuk-joon
did cause me a lot of stress,
and I got annoyed and angry at times.
But amazingly, whenever we went
on a date and I saw his face,
I felt happy, and we always had fun.
Goodness.
So things like that
made me think I must like him a lot.
That's how I feel right now,
and I want to keep getting to know him.
Firstly, thanks for coming.
Of course.
If you didn't come out today,
I was going to throw you into the water.
Just like I planned to do yesterday.
It's so pretty here.
I feel like we had
a special connection from the start.
We got really lucky
since we kept getting matched on dates.
I decided to call it fate.
After all that back and forth,
fate brought them together.
- A tale of fate.
- Seriously.
The phrase "fated couple"
suits them perfectly.
- It does.
- Yes.
It worked out in the end.
It's Seung-hyun.
I don't think of the final selection
as a confession of love.
I think it's just about picking
the person you're most interested in.
So I plan to pick Soo-hyun.
- Okay.
- Well done.
- Good job!
- Let's go!
- Personally, I'm rooting for them.
- Totally.
Come on, Soo-hyun.
Soo-hyun, why don't you give him a chance?
- Seung-hyun is super nervous right now.
- Yeah.
If only she could give him a chance.
Honestly, I don't know.
I feel like it's an 80-20 split.
I feel like it was fun talking to him.
I am curious, and I feel a bit nervous.
Breathe, Seung-hyun!
You're doing great.
- He's not inhaling right now.
- Breathe!
What is he looking at?
I have a feeling.
- She showed up.
- Did she?
- She did, right?
- Okay.
Did she show up?
- What made you ask?
- His eyes flickered.
- Come on, SH!
- She showed up.
- She showed up, right?
- Right?
- She turned up, right?
- Did she show up?
Gosh.
- I don't think this is the place.
She's somewhere else.
Did she pick Tae-hoon, by any chance?
Don't tell me she did.
I'm picking Tae-hoon
for the final selection.
Seriously, no way.
What? Soo-hyun…
Hyun…
This isn't it.
During my time here,
he's the person who made me
feel the most excited day to day.
When else would I feel
butterflies like this?
- That's understandable.
- She picked the person she likes.
Because we're watching…
- It's a shame.
- We're watching from the outside.
So we have a different perspective.
But she didn't get to bond
with Seung-hyun that much.
The strawberry banana smoothie is tasty.
- It played a big part.
- It did.
- They're sweet and refreshing.
- And the timing…
Honestly, I can't get over
how good it tastes either.
I feel the same way
about the blueberry smoothie.
I will respect Soo-hyun's decision.
But why?
THE FINAL SELECTION HAS ENDED
Expressing my feelings like that
is something I've never done before.
So it was nice to have that experience.
I'm not really the type to have regrets.
So I don't think I regret anything.
I don't feel regretful.
- He was Season Two's ray of sunshine.
- He was.
Did he down it?
- He looks breezy.
- Good for him.
Well done, Seung-hyun.
I wonder if she still
has her hopes up while she waits.
I made a decision in my mind,
but I think I kept trying to avoid it.
So I was very torn.
Oh, dear.
THE FINAL SELECTION HAS ENDED
Let's go.
It's cold.
So cold.
I kind of expected it,
so I didn't feel too upset.
I feel surprisingly okay
because I feel like
I did my best at every moment.
I did everything I wanted,
so I have no regrets.
Oh, Soo-hyun. I wish you'd given
Seung-hyun a chance.
I think even Soo-hyun's parents
will feel the same way we do.
When they see this,
they'll be like, "Why did you pick him?"
"Come to your senses!"
She needs to learn.
Yeah, she does.
Oh, dear.
- It's Han-ju.
- Han-ju.
Han-ju.
I'm still not sure
what the final selection means to him.
I don't know how seriously he'll take it.
But it seems silly not to select him
since I am interested.
Why are her eyes teary?
Why does it seem like she's been crying?
Regardless of what meaning it carries,
I thought it was a good way
of expressing my feelings.
HAN-JU'S FINAL SELECTION: JIN-WOO
I'm rooting for them too.
These two are also… Wait.
- Come on, Jin-woo.
- Jin-woo.
- Just once…
- Just talk to her.
Just, you know…
Yeah.
One of the things that mattered
to me the most coming on this show
was making sure to walk away
without any regrets.
But I'm still not sure what to do.
- Han-ju likes everything about you.
- Yes!
Yeah, and she's a Korean medicine doctor,
just like Jeong-eun.
Exactly!
But Han-ju likes you just as you are!
Can you hear me?
No, you can't.
- My hands are sweating.
- Just go on one date after the show.
Just talk to her.
I'm not saying you should commit.
Think about
what the final selection means.
- Just talk to her.
- Think about what it means.
- Open.
- Please.
Open it.
Please.
I will be heartbroken,
but I've prepared myself.
Success!
See? Look at that!
- Yes!
- You need to go for the one who likes you.
That's right.
- Han-ju was crying happy tears.
- I almost passed out.
- That's what it was.
- Did she cry?
- Did she?
- She cried happy tears.
- I'm so happy for this couple!
- Gosh, Han-ju…
JIN-WOO, HAN-JU
FINAL SELECTION
Why did you come?
Why did I come?
How could you say that?
My mind changed a lot
over the last two days.
Since the beginning,
I'd never ruled Han-ju out.
She has always been
very forward about her feelings for me,
so she caught my attention at the start.
And I think that kept coming to mind,
so I was tempted to give it a try.
I was surprised.
And I was happy.
I was also very grateful.
- I'm so happy for her.
- Great job, Han-ju's father-in-law.
- I'm like his dad.
- You're in-laws now.
Yeah, we're in-laws.
He looks like Dex today.
He looks so handsome today.
- He looks so suave.
- That's our second couple!
How great. We have two couples.
So this is how it ends. My gosh.
In the same way
that we requested dates
for the chance to talk a bit more,
I chose you for the final selection
because I'm curious.
Even after the show,
I want to keep getting to know you
back in the real world.
That's the mindset I came here with,
like requesting a date.
- Yes, go on a date.
- Jin-woo took the initiative this time.
This is how it starts.
Very honest.
- Let's keep getting to know each other.
- Okay.
I tried to be more open and honest
so that I didn't waste this chance
because I felt like
that was my biggest weakness.
SU-JI
OPTED OUT OF FINAL SELECTION
I don't have any big regrets.
JUNG-YUN
OPTED OUT OF THE FINAL SELECTION
So I decided
not to make a final selection.
I will not make a final selection.
I won't be making a final selection.
JEONG-EUN
OPTED OUT OF THE FINAL SELECTION
It was such a heartfelt story.
- Yeah.
- Take Hyun-seo, for example.
She was all in from the start.
- And Han-ju was the same.
- It was always Jin-woo for her.
Hang on. I want to see
which of my pictures they used.
Mine are all kind of cheeky.
It's embarrassing to see my own photos.
If there was alcohol around,
I used to just drink it all.
But since I know he doesn't
like people who get drunk,
I think I naturally
held back from drinking.
That's good.
Love changed her.
And I used to think
if you're charming and attractive,
guys would naturally be drawn to you,
but now I think
being honest about your feelings
is what makes someone attractive.
I think the most obvious change in me
will be a huge boost in confidence.
Now that I've experienced rejection,
when it comes to opening up to people,
I don't think I'll feel
anxious anymore about trying.
They're not giving us the new releases.
You've already read mine anyway.
Oh my gosh.
I really wanted to see these.
This is such a precious memory!
We finally get to look.
I've already read yours.
But it must be new to you.
- I wanted to read it.
- Here. It's a gift.
It's an honor.
Thank you.
You were so cute.
- Right?
- Yeah, so bright-eyed.
I appreciate how expressive he's been,
and he gave me a lot of good memories,
so I'm grateful to him for that.
And I want to keep getting to know him.
I thought it was fate from the start.
Feeling curious about someone
was a very new feeling for me.
And it didn't just end there.
She made me want to keep seeing her again.
So that's a huge deal to me.
I would like to consider this
our first day as an official couple.
We'd better take a close look
at these when we get back.
Right? It's so fun.
- Right?
- Yeah.
I've changed so much.
Before I joined the show,
I was a colorless person.
I didn't feel any big emotions,
and I was like a robot.
But since coming on this show,
I felt so many
different types of emotions.
So I feel like I can start living life
with a different attitude.
I've been thinking that a lot.
I think the big change is
that I now have a more positive mindset.
The nature of my job
requires looking for flaws
and running calculations
to identify weaknesses.
And I was really bad
at taking compliments.
But I learned that it's okay
to accept compliments sometimes.
During my time here,
I thought a lot about love and dating
and reflected on myself a lot.
So I feel like I've matured a little.
I was always very self-conscious and
hyper-aware of other people's reactions,
but I was able to overcome that,
and I've grown a lot mentally.
I think I achieved everything I aimed for.
I've never told someone
I liked them before.
But now I know
that it's not something to be scared of.
I was always really good
at hiding my emotions,
and I found it hard
to express my feelings.
And I wanted to overcome that.
This big change in me
will probably amaze
the people who know me.
But this is the new me.
I feel like I've been reborn.
It was a fascinating experience.
You don't feel emotions
like this every day.
But I'm already feeling this way,
so I found that really amazing
above all else.
I got to meet such great people,
so every day was really precious.
It felt like
a once-in-a-life time experience.
I really want to stay in touch
with all of them.
When I look back on this time later,
I think it will feel like a dream.
And I kind of look forward
to the kind of person I will be
after the show.
Subtitle translation by: Hannah Og Nam